That will come for the regular Skettermine Monocity Council for Tuesday, January 20, 2026.
I'm too public input on Skettermine Monocity Council for Personal Parenthesis, have none.
Three A, Proclamation, the Action on the Proclamation, the Clearing January 21, 2026, as P.E. O. Day.
That's philanthropic educational organization.
Thank you.
I was going to mess that one up.
That's what I said to me today.
Motion to approve.
Second.
Hi.
Jones.
Borker.
Hi.
And three B, Proclamation, the Clearing January 31, 2026, as not to go yesterday.
Motion to approve.
Thank you.
Hi.
Jones.
Borker.
Hi.
Parker.
That's a sad day.
So we're going to do the BO Day room.
We'll come back with a picture and then we'll be going on.
My body's gone.
This is probably fun.
This is a pretty fun day.
Here comes the office.
Stand up.
Here.
Come on.
Hold on.
We'll be back.
Come on.
Don't go for a drive.
No.
I don't know if I take this because I have to take one in turn, is that right?
How am I supposed to do that?
Somebody is taking pictures of me.
I'm going to see that one.
Yes, ma'am.
Please.
I don't know if he did that one.
All right, there's a party.
Yeah, I get it.
I get it.
You're fine.
That's fine.
You're going to be proud.
Oh, yeah.
I'm fine.
We appreciate all of you.
We appreciate you.
So, suits.
Suit.
You're having Kate, you're having Kate?
How's your name?
Yes.
What about sandwiches?
I don't.
You're fine.
We're fine.
That could now.
I.
Good video.
Take a break of the video.
Don't write it down.
Sure.
Yeah.
How to use it.
There are videos on music, right?
Yeah.
It's like I made that video.
She told me to make this video.
You know, and I made this video.
video and I went in the next day and she said, I don't know, I should help you or choke you.
We got slammed after that.
We got people coming everywhere.
Part of the policy, job, of course, we have people from here on the phone.
It has been wonderful.
We appreciate all of our accounting.
It's out when we need a help.
We can be one of them.
I mean, I was telling somebody today that how special
jobs grow, she had been there at the community over the years.
There's probably no lady chief, I don't know if he did.
But as kids, we all went to the office.
No matter how old you are in this room.
As a kid, you went to the office and, you know,
the adults were taking our drink and it's not.
We're going to miss you, of course.
But we also want you to enjoy your time.
I want to see you soon.
What are you doing here?
You don't kill it.
Does you know how to drive this drink sweeper?
All right, let's raise it up for a time list.
Mr. Brouff, second.
E-step.
Hi.
Barnes, hi.
Parker.
Hi.
4B, minutes from the January 6th, 206, regular meeting.
Most of the proves second.
Doctor.
Hi.
James.
Barnes, hi.
Parker.
All right.
4C, budget amendment 26, that's 0.
So this budget amendment is just, um,
the second part is, um, we're seeing in some different library.
And the third, so full.
Hi.
Thank you, Chris.
E-step.
All right.
Parker.
Hi.
4B, vote on recommended airport logo.
We know you love it.
Just set there and be good.
I do.
I think it's a great idea.
So when I came over there for one thing, we talked about this.
You know, we're going to start a basis and,
Laurie, kind of our dress.
You and the pilot.
Kind of what?
Two months.
Three months.
So it's representing the feathers.
Are representing the nine tribes.
Through the city.
In the end.
I'm right.
The plane.
Uh, in the mornings.
And then this was pretty, or heritage, and flying in the United.
So we are taking this in a hydraulic council.
Show them they, in questions they like to do.
And I'll kind of let more of you know, such as you guys,
and the table, and how we got to this pool.
Actually, the yellow, too, also, was the old hanger.
Or, yes.
We used it for the old hanger.
Yeah, all around the barrel for the old hanger.
Yeah.
So I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm doing brainic.
It's everybody up here.
I saw such a opportunity to, uh, the greatest chairman.
Uh, so, I tried to incorporate that, that set up because there's, I think there's six of those,
famous centers.
One other one's on home.
But, honesty is happening.
Uh, the number one school is in total Texas.
So I thought, you know, having that opportunity to honor it.
Um, the other thing is, you know, this one, I want to.
Oh, I know this, though, when I want a fushing capabilities, the car was kind of painting.
Cause type of, they are kind of painted out of the駙s better, but it's very marked with this.
And so, when I look at this, I wanted to assemble that.
Put it up to these, so on this page this one just fits in the different assessing HAHAH.
That was a horizontal vis-re resemble this one's vertical.
So this one, you can put on the defense.
And that's other way that I, this could be able to talk
This is a version that goes on back to someone's student,
aren't going to present the version that will go on.
It's got to work in black and white, but so this is the black and white version.
Literally, that's where I start.
It's getting it looking great in black and white before it becomes published.
That was literally the first one.
Because there will be a lot of times that she just take on this.
Let's say if somebody's building document and have dark photo,
then look at the logo top of it, that's the white version that goes on with that.
There's a lot of ways to know the expressions of the logo use.
I think it is.
This is the guy who made the car key.
This is the one we get to use first.
We got it.
Whatever they got it, our force is making a statement.
They make market points.
So there's opportunity for them to leave with something that's better.
There's also, you know, they have great experience.
There's events there.
They will buy this.
It's not a slide.
It's a slide.
So I've got that designed into it.
So that we can use it.
It's a sign on there.
It would be a slide.
You have to see how first of all it is.
My goal here too was to create something that's possible with being a part of the car.
And it's part of the world.
It's too hard.
And then we'll build it in a modern car.
I would like to add like to that. She is terrific. The idea is to get our name out there.
I would like to add things that we're talking about.
Absolutely.
I don't know if I look at it.
Yeah, I was burdened.
Really, thank you.
So are we just approving all of these?
That's all the same.
Just different kinds of things.
First of all, thank you.
Thank you.
It changed a little in the city.
It was done.
It's time for the airport to have a check.
It's time for all over.
And what's that?
Senior center, it's time for the airport to have a check.
What's the new airport?
All the airport.
A lot of it.
Broad okay.
Don't talk to us.
We can't take it.
Can't take it.
T6 text in on there.
That is.
That's what I read.
When I was at the leadership, my amen.
At the airport.
I actually docked staffer did a lot too.
There's so many people.
He worked a lot with you.
On.
Absolutely.
Thank you.
For me.
There's no action.
From that to the letter date, for a resolution CC-2026-02,
current patient's mind will go in with code of ordinances to include self-muth-202.
This is the orderly adoption of the ordinance that we have to do first that year.
Push to approve.
Excuse me.
Hi.
Hello.
All right.
For G joint resolution, I'm issue A-2026-01-C-C-2026-03.
I'll throw out an Indian-byte sport, the E-Live, and for a generalist,
or a dumb lesson, play that commercial structure at 1.20-0.
1.20-0.
So, are they getting along with the V-A process?
Hi.
For June-Sight, E-STIP.
For H proposed, conflict of mentors policy and resolution CC-2026,
that's the report of the conference of mentors policy consistent with,
and incorporate the conflict of mentors standards of state local home of writing for
acceptability, implementation, providing for severability, and effective date.
This is a policy that we really should have had very long time ago,
in order to have certain grants.
But the ARPA grant brought to fruition.
I had in my notes when we went abroad at two weeks that we needed it.
I already had in my notes that we needed it for our opioid grants.
So, it's just basically adopting ethics rule four, state ethics rule four,
and saying that you cannot financially gain from your position on the count of four.
Can you keep me out of jail?
Well, keep you out of jail.
I mean, following that rule.
What do you do?
That's what I'm asking.
Most of you approve that.
Second, you go to stand.
Jones.
I'm sorry.
You're called?
Hi.
Parker.
The new business, we've been posting for resins in post-medus agenda.
Six staff of work.
Seven mayor council.
It means now some of us have been.
So have been, I found out last week that we
thought about what that was.
But that's the last week that Milo was awarded the 20,
26 summer marriage conference.
100 marriage.
From a process, for years, on their spouse,
it'll be yours.
It's a, it's a, it's a, it's a,
it's a, it's a, it's a, it's a, it's a,
it's a, it's a, it's a, it's a, it's a, we,
it's a, it's a, it's a, it's a, it's a, it's a, it's a,
with Edmund, Heavitt, California,
Mime on an album, and Mayors voted, and they voted for us.
So, it was a pretty good, pretty a deal for us.
My heart Edmund needed to California as a whole,
but it was because so, and we did find out that we didn't know
a head-on that we're trying to purchase here.
But we did find out, we intended to call them,
and talk to the poster, O.M.L. and the sponsorship and grants
to help pay for this thing.
So, we weren't aware of it at the beginning,
so that's a little bit helpful.
So, I think that was all I have with the details.
Hello, sir.
Hey, you're welcome.
Hey, city manager communications.
I made a before you forget Mr. Dunkhol is also going to drive
one of the buses.
Yes, it's the bus.
Oh, yeah.
Yes.
She said he said he said he'd say he'd say he'd say.
She ain't got a boat.
I got a bus permit.
Missy has one thing, but I was supposed to.
Everybody to be weather aware.
I know that there's lots of forecast, you know,
showing snow.
We've been getting ready on the utility side.
And in the street apartment side, I'm, you know,
clearing snow.
So I mean, we'll be ready.
We've got a boat.
Yeah.
She watched this afternoon and update.
So what are they saying right now?
I'll be enough on the seat.
Where?
Where is it?
There's the line in the right.
I thought we'd come back, right?
What do you think you think?
Right around the two of us.
He's like, right in the middle of the head.
We get you don't want him.
Hey, don't forget to turn around, don't drown.
I don't want him.
I don't want him to drown.
I just don't want him to drown.
Just.
Be careful, because I'm your backup.
Yeah.
I lost my missed you.
I mean, bring up, there's a recent, there was a recent, what court case.
Supreme court case.
Supreme court.
That we have to have in the board's packet, 24 hours of advance, before you vote it.
I know there's sometimes things are changing.
I mean, you know, as, as I'm going to get closer to time.
So, I mean, this is just a good example of the wheels of turn really, really slow.
So, I mean, if there's something that we don't have it ready, within 24 hours,
or within 24 hours, which is aimed to the board, and then we'll just have to put on the next meeting.
We can't bring you an updated, whatever, it is a violation that will be made in fact, which is a misdemeanor.
I mean, that's a name.
I don't know if it's in the agreement with the analysis.
That's a specific course.
Well, we've got all the rules, but we end up in jail.
I'm too pretty for jail.
We're good, buddy.
I must follow rules.
Missy scares us.
I should.
Yes, sir.
Nine adjournments.
Motion.
Second.
Open.
All right.